moralstories.org 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy • Moral Stories

moralstories.org is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  moralstories.org may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

 **We Collect following when you Submit a Story or Post Comment**

· Name  
· Email Address (Only if posting a comment through our Website / Not Required on our App)  
· Demographic Information such as City, State, and Country (Optional / Not Required on our App)

 **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **How we use cookies**

A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

A cookie is stored temporarily and the user can clear it by cleaning browser history, cookies, cache etc.  User browser may store or cache a temporary copy of a webpage to your hard drive for a faster loading of a website.  The only information we keep on our server is your name, email address, IP address if you have submitted it through comment or contact form on our website. We do not transfer your name or email address to any 3rd party for any purpose at all. We use google analytics and your demographic, type of device data is used anonymously to help us improve our user experience.

Like many other Web sites, www.moralstories.org makes use of log files. These files merely log visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.moralstories.org uses cookies to store information about visitor’s preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **Our Advertising Partners**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.  These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on www.moralstories.org and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.moralstories.org. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to www.moralstories.org and other sites on the Internet.  Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

www.moralstories.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

 **Third Party Privacy Policies**

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.moralstories.org’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **For Using Our App**

Our app is for the reading purpose only.  Your google play store account information is used to verify your device compatibility, download and update our app during the installation process as per your consent.  Through our app, we do not directly collect or transfer any data on our servers which may violate your privacy. We do not accept comments or stories through our app as it does not contain any form built in it.

 **Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.
